Guide to the Stanford University Postcard Collection
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Postcards (individual)
  - South East Corner, Undated; 560; Color Print
    Message: Hello Frances:- Well I am back at Stanford at last. I brought the coon back with me, and she behaved fine. College starts on the 1st of September. This is rushing season now and I am pretty busy. I hope to see you soon. You had better run down here in a machine. All of the fellows went crazy over Pete. We turn her loose in the day time, and she has broken about every thing in the house but we don't care for that. my address is DTD House, Stanford University, Cal.
    Addressed to Miss Frances La Place, Camp Meeker, Sonoma County, Calif.
  - South East Corner, Undated; 561; Color Print
    Caption: South East View of Stanford University, California
  - Quad Front View - pre 1906, Undated; 562; Sepia Print
    Caption: Facade Stanford University Quadrangle - Compliments First National Bank Palo Alto, Cal.
    Quad Front View - pre 1906
  - Quad Front View - pre 1906, Undated; 563; B/W Print
    Caption: Facade Stanford University Quadrangle
    Addressed to: A. B. Shaw, 353 Melville Av., Palo Alto, Cal.
  - Quad Front View - pre 1906, Undated; 564; Photo
    Message: Dear A. I will have to stay at Stanford until 6:30 so if you come tonight don't try to get the 5:00. Everything fine. Hoping to see you. as always EH
    Addressed to: Mr. A. S. Kalenborn, #911 Shreve Building, San Francisco, California
  - Quad Front View - pre 1906, Undated; 565; B/W Print
    Caption: Leland Stanford Jr. University, Front View, Palo Alto, Cal.
    Message: "Hello Monkey:" Say I just can't come home. having the best time of my life. I am going to telegraph Mr. Terry to day for another week. Al
    Addressed to: Monkey Griffith, 817 Preston St., Louisville, Ky
  - Quad Front View - pre 1906, Undated; 566; Tinted Print
    Caption: 5082 General View fo Stanford University, California
  - Quad Front View - pre 1906, Undated; 567; B/W Print
    Caption: 7285 Stanford University Palo Alto, Cal. Bird's Eye View
  - Quad Front View - pre 1906, Undated; 568; Photo
    Caption: No. 110 Front View Outer Quadrangle. Stanford University Palo Alto, California.
  - Quad Front View - pre 1906, Undated; 569; Color Print
    Caption: Front View Stanford University, Cal.
    Message: Dear bena- We are here in Menlo Park waiting for the train. There is a crowd of 29. We all intoxicated. Mary Crissith
    Addressed to: Mrs. Albena Ferrieth, Carson City, Nevada
  - Quad Front View - pre 1906, Undated; 570; Color Print
    Caption: Leland Stanford Jr. University (Front View) showing Memorial Arch, Palo Alto, Cal.
  - Quad Front View - pre 1906, Undated; 571; Color Print
    Caption: Birdseye View of the Leland Stanford Jr. University, Palo Alto, Cal.
    Imprint: Britton and Rey
  - Quad Front View - pre 1906, Undated; 572; Color Print
    Caption: Birdseye View of Stanford University, California
  - Quad Front View - pre 1906, Undated; 573; Color Print
    Caption: No. 16 Stanford University, California
  - Quad Front View - pre 1906, Undated; 574; Color Print
    Caption: Stanford University, California
    Imprint: Richard Brendt
  - Quad Front View - pre 1906, Undated; 575; Photo
    Stanford before the earthquake
    gift of Mrs. J. F. Cutler 4/17/60
  - Quad Front View - pre 1906, Undated; 576; Color Print
    Caption: Stanford University, California.
  - Quad Front View - pre 1906, Undated; 577; Color Print
    Caption: 759 - North Facade, Stanford University, California.
  - Quad Front View - pre 1906, Undated; 578; B/W Print
    Caption: Fornt of Outer Quadrangle, Stanford University, California 7351
    Addressed to: Mrs. James N. Hays, 201 S. Grand Ave., Los Angeles, Cal.
  - Quad Front View - pre 1906, Undated; 579; Color Print
    Caption: Front View, Stanford University
    Gift of Mrs. Esther Griffen Given 11/8/56; includes image of Quake damage to Arch
  - Quad Front View - pre 1906, Undated; 580; Color Print
    Caption: The Leland Stanford Jr. University Palo Alto, Cal. Lydia E. Pinkham's Vegetable Compound is in three forms, liquid, lozenges, pills. Blood Purifier, Liver Pills, Sanative Wash, For all Female Complaints.
    gift of Helen Shepherd 9/26/74
  - Quad Front View - pre 1906, Undated; 581; B/W Print
  - Quad Front View - pre 1906, Undated; 582; Color Print
    Caption: General View Stanford University, Palo Alto, Cal. 5216
  - Quad Front View - pre 1906, Undated; 583; Color Print
    Caption: 8572. Main Entrance and Memorial Arch, Leland Stanford Jr. University
  - Quad Front View - pre 1906, Undated; 584; B/W Print
    Caption: Entrance to Quadrangle Stanford University, Cal.
  - Quad Front View - pre 1906, Undated; 585; Color Print
    Caption: 8573. Main Entrance and Memorial Arch, Leland Stanford Jr. University
    Message: having a good time. We are all with you in spirit. Love to you all. K.
    addressed to: Miss Anne River, c/o Mrs. G. F. Oliver, 10th and Alden Sts., Portland, Oregon.
  - Quad Front View - pre 1906, Undated; 586; Photo
    Caption: No. 106. Memorial Arch, Stanford University, Palo Alto, California.
  - Quad Front View - pre 1906, Undated; 587; Color Print
  - Quad Front View - pre 1906, Undated; 588; Photo
    Message: [illegible]
    addressed to: Miss Isabel McCracken, 1279 - 20th Ave., East Oakland, California
  - Quad Front View - pre 1906, Undated; 589; Photo
    Caption: No. 112. West View Stanford University. Palo Alto, California.
  - Quad Front View - pre 1906, Undated; 590; B/W Print
    Caption: Science Buildings, Stanford University, Cal.
    Addressed to: Mr. Hubert O. Jenkins, 85 Pinckney St., Boston, Mass.
  - Quad Front View - pre 1906, 5/19/1898; 591; B/W Print
    Caption: The Completed Quadrangle, Stanford University, Cal.
  - Quad - Front Views - Post 1906, Undated; 592; B/W Print
    Quad - Front Views - Post 1906
  - Quad - Front Views - Post 1906, Undated; 593; B/W Print
    Caption: Front View - Stanford University, Cal.
    Imprint: Cardinell - Vincent Co.
  - Quad - Front Views - Post 1906, Undated; 594; Color Print
    Caption: Front View, Stanford University, California. S - 567. Front View - Stanford University, Cal.
  - Quad - Front Views - Post 1906, Undated; 595; Color Print
  - Quad - Front Views - Post 1906, Undated; 596; Photo
    Caption: Stanford University, Cal. 255
  - Quad - Front Views - Post 1906, Undated; 597; Sepia Print
    Caption: General View fo Stanford University. Cal. 1849
  - Quad - Front Views - Post 1906, Undated; 598; Color Print
    Caption: 1895 - General View of Stanford University, California.
  - Quad - Front Views - Post 1906, Undated; 599; Photo
    Caption: Stanford University, Cal. 258.
  - Quad - Front Views - Post 1906, Undated; 600; Photo
  - Quad - Front Views - Post 1906, Undated; 601; Photo
    Caption: The Front of Stanford University
  - Quad - Front Views - Post 1906, Undated; 602; Photo
  - Quad - Front Views - Post 1906, Undated; 603; B/W Print
  - Quad - Front Views - Post 1906, Undated; 604; Photo
    Caption: A View of Stanford University, Cal. 3846.
  - Quad - Front Views - Post 1906, Undated; 605; Photo
    Caption: A View of Stanford University, Cal. 3846
    Imprint: The Western Card Co.
    Addressed to: Miss Bealala Albright, Great Valley, NY
  - Quad - Front Views - Post 1906, Undated; 606; Sepia Print
    Caption: 1504 - North Facade, Leland Stanford Jr. University, Palo Alto, California.
    Message: An outer arcade, similar to the inner arcade around the inner court, passes entirely around the buildings on the outside under their buildings. These buildings from the front of the outer quadrangle. The buildings are an adaptation of the od Spanish mission architecture of California. - of buff sandstone and red tiled roofs. My laboratory is in the building marked x.
  - Quad - Front Views - Post 1906, Undated; 607; B/W Print
    Caption: No. 44. Stanford University, California.
  - Quad - Front Views - Post 1906, Undated; 608; Color Print
    Caption: Stanford University, Palo Alto, California. Stanford University. Stanford University, at Palo Alto, California, in the world-famous Santa Clara Valley, is one of the Nation's outstanding universities. This is a view of its front facade.
  - Quad - Front Views - Post 1906, Undated; 609; Sepia Print
    Caption: 1903 - North Facade, Stanford University, California.
  - Quad - Front Views - Post 1906, Undated; 610; Color Print
    Imprint: Edw H. Mitchell
  - Quad - Front Views - Post 1906, Undated; 611; Color Print
    Caption: 1504:- North Facade, Leland Stanford Jr. University, Palo Alto, California.
  - Quad - Front Views - Post 1906, Undated; 612; Color Print
  - Quad - Front Views - Post 1906, Undated; 613; Color Print
    Caption: No. 3. Stanford University, California
  - Quad - Front Views - Post 1906, Undated; 614; Color Print
    Imprint: The Stanford Bookstore
  - Quad - Front Views - Post 1906, Undated; 615; Color Print
    Caption: Library - Stanford University. Palo Alto. Cal.
  - Quad - Front Views - Post 1906, Undated; 616; Photo
  - Quad - Front Views - Post 1906, Undated; 617; Photo
    Caption: Stanford View
  - Quad - Front Views - Post 1906, Undated; 618; Photo
    Message: 454 Hamilton Ave. Palo Alto, Calif. Read the book and the card from Mabel, handkerchiefs and card from Bessie, package and letter from Charlie, etc. End semester examination reports are not out yet, but it does not worry me any this time. Am goind to San Francisco to morrow. Shall write to somebody soon. H.A. Holden.
    Addressed to: Mrs. H. C. Holden, Ticonderoga, New York
  - Quad - Front Views - Post 1906, Undated; 619; Photo
  - Quad - Front Views - Post 1906, Undated; 620; Color Print
    Caption: General View of Stanford University, Palo Alto, California 434. Stanford University is located in the Santa Clara Valley at Palo Alto, thirty miles south of San Francisco. The site consists of 8800 acres, -campus proper 1500 acres- and was founded in 1887 by Senator and Mrs. Leland Stanford as a memorial to their son. Student attendance numbers over 4000. The first class was held in 1891.
  - Quad - Front Views - Post 1906, Undated; 621; Photo
  - Quad - Front Views - Post 1906, Undated; 622; Color Print
    Caption: General View Stanford University, California. 6579.
  - Quad - Front Views - Post 1906, Undated; 623; Color Print
    Caption: 37 Front View Stanford University, California
  - Quad - Front Views - Post 1906, Undated; 624; Color Print
    Caption: Stanford University, Quadrangle from Palm Drive, Stanford University, Stanford, Calif.
  - Quad - Front Views - Post 1906, Undated; 625; Photo
  - Quad - Front Views - Post 1906, Undated; 626; Color Print
    Caption: 10610. Stanford University, Palo Alto, Cal.
    Addressed to: Mrs. E. C. Nortore, Nevada City. Cal. B4359
  - Quad - Front Views - Post 1906, Undated; 627; Photo
  - Quad - Front Views - Post 1906, Undated; 628; B/W Print
    Caption: Stanford University, Cal.
  - Quad - Front Views - Post 1906, Undated; 629; B/W Print
  - Quad - Front Views - Post 1906, Undated; 630; B/W Print
  - Quad - Front Views - Post 1906, Undated; 631; Sepia Print
    Caption: Front View of Stanford University, Cal. 1841
  - Quad - Front Views - Post 1906, Undated; 632; Photo
  - Quad - Front Views - Post 1906, Undated; 633; Photo
  - Quad - Front Views - Post 1906, Undated; 634; Photo
  - Quad - Front Views - Post 1906, Undated; 635; Photo
  - Quad - Front Views - Post 1906, Undated; 636; Photo
    Caption: Roble Corner Stanford University.
  - Quad - Front Views - Post 1906, Undated; 637; Photo
  - Quad - Front Views - Post 1906, Undated; 638; B/W Print
  - Quad - Front Views - Post 1906, Undated; 639; Photo
  - Quad - Front Views - Post 1906, Undated; 640; B/W Print
    Caption: Front View. Stanford University, Cal.
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 641; Photo
    Quad - Inner
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 642; Photo
    Caption: Arch, Stanford University, California
    Imprint: J.C. Badell
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 643; Photo
    Caption: Inner Quadrangle, Stanford University, Cal.
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 644; Photo
    Caption: The East Arch, Stanford University, Cal.
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 645; Photo
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 646; Photo
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 647; Photo
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 648; Photo
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 649; Photo
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 650; Photo
    Caption: 356 Entrance to Quadrangle
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 651; B/W Print
    Caption: West Entrance to Quad, Stanford University, Cal.
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 652; Color Print
    Caption: 5217. Quadrangle, Stanford University
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 653; B/W Print
    Caption: Quadrangle and Arches, Stanford University, Cal. 1850.
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 654; Sepia Print
    Caption: Quadrangle - Leland Stanford Jr. University, Palo Alto, Cal.
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 655; Sepia Print
    Caption: Quadrangle and Arches, Stanford University, Cal.
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 656; Color Print
    Caption: Stanford University, California, on Road of a Thousand Wonders
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 657; Photo
    Caption: Quadrangle, Leland Stanford Jr. University, Palo Alto, California 87.
    Imprint: Bardell-O'Neill
    Addressed to: Mrs C. F. Fiedmann, 1725 Sacreamento St., Vallejo, Calif.
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 658; Color Print
    Caption: Stanford University, Memorial Arch, Inner Quadrangle, Stanford University. In the background is Hoover Tower. This academic center of the University is contructed of native sandstone in a classic Romanesque style typical of Mediterranean civilizations. Stonecutters from Italy carved the intricate patterns on arches and column capitals. The Inner and Outer Quadrangles include 12 major academic buildings and Memorial Church, and encompasses 17 acres.
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 659; Sepia Print
    Caption: 1898-West End of Inner Quadrangle, Stanford University, California.
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 660; Color Print
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 661; Color Print
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 662; Photo
    Message: Merry Christmas and Happy New Year from Your brother. H. A. Holden.
    Addressed to: Mrs. M. A. Foster, Ticonderoga, New York.
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 663; Color Print
    Caption: No. 38. Inner Quadrangle Stanford University, California.
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 664; Photo
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 665; Photo
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 666; Sepia Print
    Caption: 1505 - Through the Arches, Leland Stanford Jr. University, Palo Alto, California.
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 667; B/W Print
    Caption: Arcade - Stanford University
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 668; B/W Print
    Caption: East Arch - Stanford University
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 669; B/W Print
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 670; B/W Print
    Caption: Arcades, Stanford University, Cal.
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 671; B/W Print
    Caption: S-569 The East Arches - Stanford
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 672; Color Print
    Caption: S-569: - The East Arches, Stanford University, California
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 673; Color Print
    Caption: 185. "The Quad," Leland Stanford Jr. University
    Addressed to: Mrs Albert Elkers, 1512 M St., Sacramento, Cal.
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 674; Tinted Print
    Caption: 5071 The "Quad," Stanford University, California
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 675; Color Print
    Caption: "The Quad" Stanford University, California
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 676; Sepia Print
    Caption: A Stanford University Arcade, Cal. 1847
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 677; Photo
    Caption: A Stanford Arcade Stanford University
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 678; Photo
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 679; Photo
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 680; Photo
  - Inner Quad, 3/23/1914; 681; B/W Print
    Message: Dearest Sis - Not one word have I heard from my sisters since leaving home. Esther had a letter from Henriette yesterday. she did not say how you were feeling. E and I went to the City Sat. to see the Blue Bird. I never saw anything more beautiful. glad to hear of Dorothy's success. The time is drawing near when I shall turn my face homeward. I wonder if I would ever be ready to go, feel as though I should like to stay on and on. The country is like a picture so green [illegible] I shall return Friday night. With much love. [illegible]
    Addressed to: Mrs. C. W. Thomas, Woodland, Calif.
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 682; Color Print
    Caption: 185 - "The Quad," Stanford University, California
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 683; Color Print
    Caption: 185 - The "Quad," Stanford University, California
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 684; Color Print
  - Inner Quad, 1909; 685; Color Print
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 686; Color Print
    Caption: 1918 - Arcade, Stanford University, California.
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 687; Color Print
    Caption: 415 - East Arcade and Memorial Court, Stanford University, California
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 688; Photo
    Caption: A Stanford Arcade, Stanford University
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 689; Color Print
    Caption: View of the Corridor and "Quad," Leland Stanford Jr. University, California
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 690; Color Print
    Caption: Arcade at Stanford University, Cal.Horizontal
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 691; Color Print
    Caption: Arcade, Stanford University, California
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 692; B/W Print
    Caption: 5072 Arcade, Stanford University, California
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 693; Photo
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 694; Photo
    Caption: No. 2 Corridors and Memorial Court Stanford University, Cal.
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 695; Color Print
    Caption: Arches in Memorial Court, Stanford University, Palo Alto, California, Senator Leland Stanford and Mrs. Jane Lathrop Stanford founded Leland Stanford Junior University in 1887 as a memorial to their only son. Situated at Palo Alto on the spacious Stanford Farm of 8800 acres the world famous University is picturesquely situated in delightful surroundings. Student attendance numbers over 4000. The first class was held in 1891.
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 696; B/W Print
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 697; B/W Print
    Caption: Memorial Court Stanford University, Cal.
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 698; B/W Print
    Caption: Memorial Court Stanford Unversity, Cal.
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 699; Photo
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 700; Photo
    Caption: 1901 - Quadrangle from Memorial Court, Stanford University, California.
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 701; Sepia Print
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 702; B/W Print
  - Inner Quad, 12/22/1908; 703; Tinted Print
    Message: Love to you both. Jan 22. '08. N.L.S.
    Addressed to: Miss Lillie Schlund, Claysons Ranch, Phoeniz, Arizona
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 704; B/W Print
    Caption: Leland Stanford Jr. University, Palo Alto, Cal. Take her a box of Orchid Chocolate. The Pinnacle of Perfection.
    Imprint: Boldemann's
  - Inner Quad, post 1906; 705; B/W Print
    Caption: Memorial Court, Stanford University, California. 1896
  - Inner Quad, 1896; 706; Sepia Print
    Caption: Memorial Court, Stanford University, California 1896
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 707; Photo
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 708; Sepia Print
    Caption: Corridors and Memorial Court - Stanford University, Cal.
    Message: Hello Bud How are you any how? I'm getting along bully. Had a fine time so far. The rush is tomorrow. Write if there's anything doing. Don
    Addressed to: Homer Likely, Ukiah, Cal.
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 709; B/W Print
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 710; Color Print
  - Inner Quad, 7/17/1929; 711; Color Print
    Message: Dear Mrs. Schottman and Julia.
    Just a time to tell you that I'm on a two weeks vacation at Los Gatos am just fine and enjoying the wonderful climate down here. We'll try a pay you a visit when I return. Lovingly, Frieda.
    Mrs. Schottman, Woolsey near Dana., Berkeley, California.
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 712; Tinted Print
    Caption: The East Entrance, Stanford University, California
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 713; Color Print
    Caption: The East Entrance - Stanford University, Cal.
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 714; Sepia Print
    Caption: The East Entrance - Stanford
    Message: Dear Francis, Haven't heard from you for so long. How is Virginnia. Write to me when you have time. I am at Stanford now. Love from Helen
    Addressed to: Mrs. Reside Knuckbaum, 1830 Penn St., Denver, Col.
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 715; B/W Print
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 716; Photo
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 717; B/W Print
    Caption: Arcades. Stanford University, Cal.
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 718; Photo
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 719; Photo
    Caption: A Stanford Arcade
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 720; Photo
    Caption: Stanford Arches Stanford University, Cal.
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 721; Photo
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 722; Photo
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 723; Photo
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 724; B/W Print
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 725; Photo
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 726; Photo
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 727; Photo
    Caption: Arches, Stanford University
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 728; Photo
    Caption: The Stanford Memorial Church Entrance
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 729; Photo
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 730; Photo
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 731; B/W Print
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 732; Photo
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 733; Photo
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 734; Photo
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 735; Photo
    Caption: Stanford Arches Stanford Unversityq
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 736; Photo
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 737; B/W Print
    Caption: Arches, Stanford University Cal.
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 738; Photo
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 739; Color Print
    Caption: PA3:-Arcade and Memorial Church, Stanford University, Palo Alto, California
  - Inner Quad, 7/22/1906; 740; B/W Print
    Caption: The Inner Quadrangle, Stanford University
    Message: Just starting out to inspect [illegible] Stanford. S.M.
    Imprint: H.W. Simmins
    Addressed to: Mr. J.E. Maynard, 33 Talcott Ave., Rockville, Conn.
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 741; Photo
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 742; B/W Print
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 743; Tinted Print
    Caption: Memorial Church through the Arches Stanford University, California
  - Arcade with view of Art Gallery, Undated; 744; Color Print
    Caption: 5392 Memorial Court, Stanford University, California [not accurate - shows outer arcade and view of Art Gallery
  - Outer arcade arches with view of Art Gallery, Undated; 745; Photo
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 746; B/W Print
    Caption: The Inner Quadrangle - Stanford University
    Message: The "quad," as it is popularly called, is surrounded by twelve buildings and Memorial Church. It is an inner court some two hundred yards long and proportionally long wide. There are fourteen buildings in a square around the inner quad. All are joined by arcades. Then there are twelve buildings beside.(some 40 in all) [over]
    The most expensive are Memorial Church, Chemistry building, Encina Hall for boys, New Library, New Gymnasium, Museum; some of which ar not yet finished. These six cost three of rouor million dollars. That is enought of itself to set up a small kindergarten isn't it? The other thirty-six buildings cost millions. Now if you wish to form big ideas of the wealth of the university - most of these buildings have been built of stone in the last ten years and only the interest on Stanford principal has been used. The principal remains untouched; only intrest is used for all purpose whatsoever.
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 747; B/W Print
    Caption: The Inner Quadrangle - Stanford
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 748; Photo
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 749; Photo
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 750; Color Print
    Caption: 65. Inner Quadrangle, Palo Alto, Cal.
    Imprint: H.W. Simkins
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 751; Photo
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 752; Photo
  - Inner Quad, circa 1910-1915; 753; Photo
  - Inner Quad, Undated; 754; Color Print